Guide to the Joel T. Broyhill papers, 1952-1974
George Mason University Libraries
  - HR 15991 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - HR 15992 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - HR 15993 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - HR 15994 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - HR 16261 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - HR 16308 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - HR 16355 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - HR 16366 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - HR 16511 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - HR 16531 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - HR 16645 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - HR 16659 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - HR 16724 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - HR 16728 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - HR 16813 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - HR 16850 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - HR 17131 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Motion Picture Protection (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - HR 1819 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - HR 1820 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - HR 1821 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - HR 1822 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - HR 1823 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Consumer Federation of America Evaluation (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Agriculture Information (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Authorizations and Appropriations (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Consumer Protection (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - The Nations Capitol Information File, January 3, 1973 - (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Evaluations, Critiques, etc (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Environment Information up to Campaign 72 file, January 3, 1972 - (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Federal Employees Information File, January 3, 1973 - (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Personal and Campaign Finances (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Transportation Information Campaign 72, January 3, 1973 - (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - District of Columbia, Policemen, Fireman, etc. (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Education: Information, Campaign 72 File, January 3, 1973 - (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Tax Reform Bills Introduced (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Internal Security Committee, House (National Committee Against Repressive Legislation) (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Health/Medical, Plans and Programs (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Testimonial Letters: Presidential, etc. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Pomponio Charges and Related Info. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Miller Campaign Literature, Campaign 72 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Fairfax Education Association Evaluation (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - National Education Association Evaluation (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Field and Stream Evaluation (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Voting Records (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Miller "Deadly Dozen" Charge Info. (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Campaign, 1966 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Campaign, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Campaign, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Campaign, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Radio Tapes, etc. (as received in sketchy fashion from other office, after May 1), 1973 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Bill Folder (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - A (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - B (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - C (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - D (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - E (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - F (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - G (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - H (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - J (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - K (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - L (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - M (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - N (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - O (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - P (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Q (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - R (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - S (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - T (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - U (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - V (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - W (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Y (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Z (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - January (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - February (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - April (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - May (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Jine (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - July (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - August (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - September (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - October (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - November (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - December (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Statements, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Speeches 81st (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Busing Speeches (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Statements 92nd (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Convention Center-Sports Arena (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Gun Control (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - I-66 Statement (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Military Services Act (Draft Extension Memo) (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Subject Memo (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - NEPA 6-72 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Pollution (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - School Lunch Program (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Seniority System (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Social Security Amendments (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - SST Mimeo (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Pandering Advertisements (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Subway Appropriations (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Vietnam 6-72 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Vietnam (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Vietnam Mimeo (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Arlandria Flood Project, HR 18127 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Amendments 91st Congress (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Airport Airway User Charges (see also HR 4230) (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Airport Airway User Charges (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Agriculture (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - A of A (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Army (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Commerce (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Civil Service Commission (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - D.C. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Defense (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - JTB Inquiry Pentagon Concessions (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - FCC (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - FAA (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - FTC (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - GSA (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - HEW (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - HEW-Social Security (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - HUD (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Interior (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Justice (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Judiciary (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Labor (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - LB (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - NASA (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Misc (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Navy (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - P.O. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - R.R.B. (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Selective Service System (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - State (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Transportation (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Treasury (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Veterans Administration (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Virginia (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - The White House (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - HR 2946 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - HR 2947 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - HR 2948 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - HR 2949 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - HR 2950 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - HR 2951 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - HR 2952 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - HR 2953 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - HR 2954 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - HR 2955 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - HR 2956 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - HR 2957 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - HR 2958 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - HR 2959 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - HR 3755 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - HR 4317 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - HR 4318 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - HR 5008 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - HR 5009 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - HR 5562 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - HR 6688 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - HR 6689 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - HR 7766 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - HR 811 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - HR 8212 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - HR 9273 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - HR 9697 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - HR 11340 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - HR 12048 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - HR 12624 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - HR 12764 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - HR 13188 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - HR 14460 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - HR 15359 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - HR 15431 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - HR 15729 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - HR 15783 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - HR 17424 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - HJ Res 26 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - HJ Res 383 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - HJ Res 421 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - HJ Res 468 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - HJ Res 617 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - HJ Res 624 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - HJ Res 639 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - HJ Res 979 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - HJ Res 996 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - HJ Res 1013 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - HJ Res 1025 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - H Res 201 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - H Res 640 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - H Res 938 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - H Res 1343 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - H Res 1348 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - H Con Res 234 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - H Con Res 241 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - H Con Res 248 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - H Con Res 276 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - H Con Res 279 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - H Con Res 516 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - H Con Res 521 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - H Con Res 532 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - H Con Res 604 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - HR 341 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - HR 342 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Bills Referred to Committee (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - HR 343 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - HR 344 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - HR 345 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - HR 346 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - HR 347 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - HR 348 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - HR 349 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - HR 350 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - HR 351 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - HR 1241 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - HR 1531 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - HR 1649 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - HR 1919 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - HR 2222 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - HR 2223 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - HR 2224 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - HR 2225 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - HR 2226 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - HR 2260 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - HR 2261 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - HR 2262 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - HR 2360 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - HR 2464 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - HR 2502 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - HR 2558 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - HR 2566 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - HR 2567 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - HR 2568 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - HR 2569 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - HR 2570 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - HR 2644 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - HR 2807 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - HR 3068 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - HR 3242 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - HR 3353 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - HR 3568 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - HR 3600 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - HR 3601 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - HR 3620 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - HR 3844 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - HR 3910 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - HR 3934 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - HR 3935 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - HR 16813 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - HR 4351 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - HR 4505 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - HR 4599 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - HR 4675 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - HR 4742 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - HR 4844 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - HR 4906 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - HR 4907 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - HR 4908 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - HR 5007 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - HR 5038 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - HR 5039 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - HR 5074 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - HR 5224 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - HR 5226 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - HR 5483 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - HR 5485 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - HR 5486 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - HR 5672 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - HR 5771 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - HR 5772 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - HR 5989 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - HR 6017 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - HR 6043 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - HR 6043 (cont.) (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - HR 6205 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - HR 6304 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - HR 6305 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - HR 6330 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - HR 6442 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - HR 6487 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - HR 6488 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - HR 6512 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - HR 6552 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - HR 6553 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - HR 6712 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - HR 6765 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - HR 6861 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - HR 6862 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - HR 6889 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - HR 6924 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - HR 7108 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - HR 7130 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - HR 7157 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - HR 7180 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - HR 7216 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - HR 7361 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - HR 7587 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - HR 7588 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - HR 7644 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - HR 7745 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - HR 7765 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - HR 7941 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - HR 7942 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - HR 8079 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - HR 9316 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - HR 9401 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - HR 9444 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - HR 9449 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - HR 9477 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - HR 9497 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - HR 9500 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - HR 9577 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - HR 9598 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - HR 9619 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - HR 9835 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - HR 9921 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - HR 9922 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - HR 9923 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - HR 1022 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - HR 10416 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - HR 10484 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - HR 10485 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - HR 10539 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - HR 10540 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - HR 10582 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - HR 9316 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - HR 9401 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - HR 9444 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - HR 9449 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - HR 9477 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - HR 9497 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - HR 9500 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - HR 9577 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - HR 9598 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - HR 9619 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - HR 9835 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - HR 9921 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - HR 9922 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - HR 9923 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - HR 10222 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - HR 10416 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - HR 10484 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - HR 10485 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - HR 10539 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - HR 10540 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - HR 10582 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - HR 13970 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - HR 13969 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - HR 14022 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - HR 14081 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - HR 14800 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - HR 14835 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - HR 14836 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - HR 14837 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - HR 15041 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - HR 15089 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - HR 15266 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - HR 15368 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - HR 15434, 1973 - 1974 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - HR 15457, January 1974 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - HR 15537, February 1974 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - HR 15747, March 1974 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - HR 15791, April 1974 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - HR 15820, May 1974 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - HR 15929, June 1974 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - HR 15989, July 1974 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - HR 15990, August 1974 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - HR 16068, September 1974 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - HR 16368, October 1974 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - HR 16407, 1973 - 1974 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - HR 16437 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - HR 16457 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - HR 16481 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - HR 16533 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - HR 16586 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - HR 16603 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - HR 16637 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - HR 17364 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - HR 17391 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Extension of Remarks by SAS (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Statements - Press Releases (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Statements - Press Releases, July - December 1974 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Statements - Press Releases (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Statements - Press Releases (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Statements - Press Releases (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Statements - Press Releases (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Statements - Press Releases (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Statements - Press Releases (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Statements - Press Releases (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Statements - Press Releases (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - PIPOS (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Agriculture, July 1974 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - AOFA (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Civil Service (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - District of Columbia (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - F.A.A (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - F.C.C. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - G.S.A. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Social Security H.E.W. (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - HUD (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Interior (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Judiciary (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Justice (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Labor (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - L.B. (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - NASA (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Post Office (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - RRB (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - State (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Transportation (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Treasury #2 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Treasury (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Treasury (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Veterans Adm. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Virginia (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Index (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Aeronautics (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Authorization and Appropriation Cuts (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Authorization and Appropriation Increases (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Arts and Humanities (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Atomic Energy (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Cities (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Civil Rights (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Communications (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Communism (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Conservation and Recreation (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Consumers (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Crime (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Defense (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Education (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Elections (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Environment (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Federal-State Relations (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Federal Workers (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Finance (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Fishing and Fisheries (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Foreign Aid (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Government (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Health (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Housing (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Immigration (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Industry and Business (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - International Affairs (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Labor (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Mining (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Post Office (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Poverty (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Public Works (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Roads and Highways (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Senior Citizens (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Social Security (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - Taxes (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - Tourism (Box 62, Folder 39)
  - Transportation (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - Veterans (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Vietnam (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Violence (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Water Resources (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Welfare (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Youth (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Index to Voting Record, 1973 - 1974 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Member's Individual Voting Records, 1973 - 1974 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Roll Call Subject Guide, 1973 - 1974 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Member's Individual Voting Records, 1973 - 1974 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Roll Call Subject Guide, Convened January 21, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Index to Voting Record, 1973 - 1974 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Member's Individual Voting Record, 1971 - 1972 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Roll Call Subject Guide, Convened January 21, 1971 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Index to Voting Record, 1971 - 1972 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Member's Individual Voting Record, 1971 - 1972 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Roll Call Subject Guide, Convened January 18, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Index to Voting Record, 1971 - 1972 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Individual Voting Record, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Individual Voting Record by Roll Call, 1959 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Individual Voting Record by Roll Call, 1969 - 1970 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Individual Voting Record by Roll Call, 1967 - 1968 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Individual Voting Record by Roll Call, 1953 - 1954 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Individual Voting Record by Roll Call, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Individual Voting Record by Roll Call, 1963 - 1964 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Individual Voting Record by Roll Call, 1965 - 1966 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Individual Voting Record by Roll Call, 1957 - 1958 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Private Bills (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - HR 56 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - HR 73 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - HR 220 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - HR 2191 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - HR 2745 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - HR 2746 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - HR 5747 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - HR 4230 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - HR 4570 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - HR 6659 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - HR 6741 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - HR 6947 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - HR 7443 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - HR 8146 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - HR 8430 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - HR 8511 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - HR 8591 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - HR 8618 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - HR 8645 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - HR 8868 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - HR 8924 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - HR 9007 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - HR 9110 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - HR 9154 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - HR 9290 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - HR 9356 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - HR 9512 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - HR 9357 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - HR 9358 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - HR 9602 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - HR 9902 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - HR 9947 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - HR 10136 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - HR 10219 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - HR 10295 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - HR 10568 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - HR 10717 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - HR 10718 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - HR 10768 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - HR 10871 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - HR 10872 (Box 66, Folder 8)